{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Because of the snow the cars couldn't move, _________ could the buses.",
      "a": "so",
      "b": "also",
      "c": "nor",
      "d": "either not",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Nor: used after a negative statement in order to introduce another negative statement containing a similar kind of information",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We had not gone far _________ we saw a great crowd of people .",
      "a": "before",
      "b": "after",
      "c": "as soon as",
      "d": "while",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Before: earlier than a particular event or action ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is not _________ we lose our health that we realize its value.",
      "a": "because",
      "b": "after",
      "c": "until",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Until: if something happens until a particular time, it continues and then stops at that time",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I wanted to know ___ all the members had arrived.",
      "a": "because",
      "b": "if",
      "c": "till",
      "d": "while",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- If: used to mention a fact, situation, or event that someone asks about, or is not certain about",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is three years _________ he died.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "after",
      "c": "since",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Since:  from a particular time or event in the past until the present, or in that period of time",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You can read a magazine ___ you are waiting.",
      "a": "until",
      "b": "during",
      "c": "unless",
      "d": "while",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- While: during the time that something is happening",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The report ___ President Kennedy had been killed gave me quite a shock.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "what",
      "d": "when",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n-That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you mind _________ I open the window?",
      "a": "if",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "whether",
      "d": "because",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- If:  used when making a polite request",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We do not necessarily grow wiser ___ we grow older.",
      "a": "that",
      "b": "as",
      "c": "though",
      "d": "than",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- As: used to state why a particular situation exists or why someone does something ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "No man is so old ________ he can learn.",
      "a": "that",
      "b": "as",
      "c": "when",
      "d": "but",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- But: used to connect two statements or phrases when the second one adds something different or seems surprising after the first one.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}